hobobe.com 2016-04-22

# China vacation packages & private tour guides for an authentic China experience | Jetbay

## We value your trust in us and would never misplace it.

### COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

When you purchase something from our store or provide any information by other means, including, but not limited to, our Customer Service hotlines and emails, we collect the personal data you give us such as your name, contact number, postal and email addresses, and if you make a payment directly on our website, your billing information (such as credit card number, cardholder name and expiration date). We may also require you to provide us with information about your travel and hotel preferences, frequent flyer details, feedback, testimonials and photographs of the trip which you booked with us. 

When you browse our store, we also automatically receive some information about your computer, including, but not limited to, your computer's internet protocol (IP) address, Web browser software and referring website. Additionally, we may also collect information about your online activity, such as trips viewed and bookings made. This information helps us to learn about your browser and operating system, so as to customize your user experience and inhibit fraud. 

Jetbay values your trust and is committed to protecting your privacy. This information you provide to us, collectively referred to as "Personal Information", may be collected, stored, used, disclosed and transferred only strictly according to our Privacy Statement. 

### WHAT DO WE DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

In General. We use your information for the following general purposes: to provide you with the products and services you request; to provide you with travel confirmation and updates; to manage your account, including processing bills and providing travel notifications; to communicate with you in general; to respond to your questions and comments; to allow us to contact you for customer service, if necessary; to measure interest in and improve our products, services and website; to notify you about special offers and travel-related products and services that may be of interest to you; to customise your experience on our website; to solicit information from you; to resolve disputes, collect fees or troubleshoot problems; to prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities; to enforce our Terms and Conditions; and as otherwise notified to you at the point of purchase and collection. 

Email communications. To help you take advantage of any travel-related opportunities on our website, we may send you emails about our store, new products and other updates. You may withdraw your consent for us to send such marketing messages to you at any time. 

Credit Card Information. We use sensitive billing information for the purpose of completing the travel reservations which you make with us and do not store this information. 

You may at any time choose to refuse to provide any requested information. However, this may result in your inability to complete a booking with us. For email communication, you may opt out by contacting us by email at info@jetbay.com or by postal mail to "Jetbay: Opt Out" at Suite 101-1806, 77 Van Ness Avenue, San Francisco, CA, United States 94102. 

### DISCLOSURE

We may disclose your Personal Information to third party service providers with your consent (whether implied or express). We may also disclose your Personal Information if required to do so by law, to effect a corporate transaction in connection with the corporate reorganisation of the company, or if you violate our Terms of Service. 

Other than as set out above, you will be notified when your Personal Information will be shared with third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to have us share such information. 

### THIRD-PARTY SERVICES

Third-party Service Providers ("Providers") include, but are not limited to: 

  1. Third Party Suppliers such as hotels, airlines, car rental and activity providers who fulfil your travel reservations with us. By making a reservation with us, you are authorizing us to disclose to suppliers the information required to complete the booking and to deliver the related services. Please note that these suppliers may contact you as necessary to obtain additional information for this purpose.
  2. Third Party Vendors who provide services and functions on our behalf, including, but not limited to, credit card processing, business analytics, customer service, marketing, distribution of surveys and fraud prevention. We may authorize third-party vendors to collect information on our behalf, including as needed to operate our platform features.
  3. Business Partners with whom we may jointly offer products and services.
  4. Referring Websites. If you were referred to this website from another site, we may share some information about you with that referring website.

In general, the Providers used by us will only have access to and may collect, use and disclose your Personal Information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.

However, these Providers are not controlled by Jetbay and have their own privacy policies and security practices in relation to the Personal Information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions. We thus encourage you to review the privacy statements of any Provider whose services or products you use or purchase through our website. 

For example, Jetbay currently offers the payment methods of Visa, Mastercard and Paypal. If you choose a direct payment gateway through Visa or Mastercard to complete your purchase, then the billing information will be accessed by Jetbay. If you choose to pay through Paypal, then the billing information will be subject to the privacy policy of Paypal. We would thus recommend that you review the privacy policy of Paypal. 

Moreover, some Providers may be located overseas and would thus require a transfer of your Personal Information overseas. When these Providers are located in or have facilities that are located in a different jurisdiction than either you or us, your Personal Information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that Provider or its facilities are located. 

We may also share aggregate and anonymous information with third parties, including, but not limited to, advertisers and investors. For example, we may tell investors about the number of visitors our website receives or the most popular destinations booked through our website. This information will not contain any Personal Information and will be used to improve our content and services. 

### THIRD PARTY LINKS

When you click on links on our store, they may direct you away from our site. Once you leave our store's website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Statement or our website's Terms of Service. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements. 

### SECURITY

Jetbay wants you to feel comfortable with and confident about using our platform. We make it a high priority to ensure the security and confidentiality of your Personal Information. Through implementing reasonable security precautions and following industry best practices, we make sure your information is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed. We use encryption when transferring and storing sensitive Personal Information (e.g. credit card details). We follow all PCI-DSS requirements and have implemented additional generally accepted industry standard security measures. 

### AGE OF CONSENT

By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site. 

### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Statement at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. 

If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you. 

### QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATION

If you would like to access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information, please contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at info@jetbay.com or by mail at Jetbay, to "Jetbay Legal: Privacy Compliance Officer" at Suite 101-1806, 77 Van Ness Avenue, San Francisco, CA, United States 94102.
